{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Brick \u0026 Stone Siding Repair Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40143/":{"taskOID":40143,"originalTaskOID":40143,"setID":454,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":7119,"questionDisplayText":"Repair needs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What needs to be repaired? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10890,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Leaking water or moisture","answerDisplayText":"Leaking water or moisture","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10891,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Brick or stone is loose","answerDisplayText":"Brick or stone is loose","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10892,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Discoloration of brick or stone","answerDisplayText":"Discoloration of brick or stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10893,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Brick or stone is cracked or chipped","answerDisplayText":"Brick or stone is cracked or chipped","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10894,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Missing, broken, or rusty flashing","answerDisplayText":"Missing, broken, or rusty flashing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10895,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Missing, crumbling mortar between bricks or stones","answerDisplayText":"Missing, crumbling mortar between bricks or stones","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10896,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Need to fill area after removing air conditioning unit, etc.","answerDisplayText":"Need to fill area after removing air conditioning unit, etc.","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1065,"questionDisplayText":"Current siding type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of siding do you have?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10886,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Stone Veneer","answerDisplayText":"Stone Veneer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10887,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Brick Veneer","answerDisplayText":"Brick Veneer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10888,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Real Stone","answerDisplayText":"Real Stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10889,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Real Brick","answerDisplayText":"Real Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":16749,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":7119,"questionDisplayText":"Repair needs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What needs to be repaired? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10890,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Leaking water or moisture","answerDisplayText":"Leaking water or moisture","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10891,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Brick or stone is loose","answerDisplayText":"Brick or stone is loose","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10892,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Discoloration of brick or stone","answerDisplayText":"Discoloration of brick or stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10893,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Brick or stone is cracked or chipped","answerDisplayText":"Brick or stone is cracked or chipped","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10894,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Missing, broken, or rusty flashing","answerDisplayText":"Missing, broken, or rusty flashing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10895,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Missing, crumbling mortar between bricks or stones","answerDisplayText":"Missing, crumbling mortar between bricks or stones","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10896,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Need to fill area after removing air conditioning unit, etc.","answerDisplayText":"Need to fill area after removing air conditioning unit, etc.","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10890,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Leaking water or moisture","answerDisplayText":"Leaking water or moisture","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10891,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Brick or stone is loose","answerDisplayText":"Brick or stone is loose","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10892,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Discoloration of brick or stone","answerDisplayText":"Discoloration of brick or stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10893,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Brick or stone is cracked or chipped","answerDisplayText":"Brick or stone is cracked or chipped","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10894,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Missing, broken, or rusty flashing","answerDisplayText":"Missing, broken, or rusty flashing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10895,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Missing, crumbling mortar between bricks or stones","answerDisplayText":"Missing, crumbling mortar between bricks or stones","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10896,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Need to fill area after removing air conditioning unit, etc.","answerDisplayText":"Need to fill area after removing air conditioning unit, etc.","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1065,"questionDisplayText":"Current siding type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of siding do you have?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10886,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Stone Veneer","answerDisplayText":"Stone Veneer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10887,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Brick Veneer","answerDisplayText":"Brick Veneer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10888,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Real Stone","answerDisplayText":"Real Stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10889,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Real Brick","answerDisplayText":"Real Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":16749,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10886,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Stone Veneer","answerDisplayText":"Stone Veneer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10887,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Brick Veneer","answerDisplayText":"Brick Veneer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10888,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Real Stone","answerDisplayText":"Real Stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10889,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Real Brick","answerDisplayText":"Real Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":16749,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"__cache./api/resource/task/40143/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40143,"taskName":"Brick or Stone Siding: Repair or Partially Replace","taskDescription":"Repair or Partially Replace Brick or Stone Siding","xmTaskDescriptor":"Brick \u0026 Stone Siding Repair Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":220,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Brick masonry mason local wall","textMessagingName":"Repr Mason Siding","rolloverLongDesc":"True brick \u0026 stone siding should last a lifetime with proper maintenance \u0026 tuck-pointing. Today, popular alternatives to stone \u0026 brick are veneer finishes.","rolloverShortDesc":"Repair damaged bricks or stones or mortar","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair or Partially Replace Brick or Stone Siding.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Stone \u0026 Brick Siding Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":16,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Brick or Stone Siding Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Brick or Stone Siding: Repair or Partially Replace","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Brick and Stone Siding Project","urlName":"Brick-or-Stone-Siding-Repair-or-Partially-Replace","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Stone \u0026 Brick Siding Repair Pros - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Brick,masonry,mason,local,wall,walkway,walk,steps,sidewalks,patio,bricks,paver,flooring,Stone,Siding,Partially,floor","emcCategoryOid":-12008,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":454,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}